bookmarkshut.info 2015-05-15

# BookmarksHut - Your Source for Social News and Networking

## Privacy Statement

Bookmarkshut is committed to protecting your Personal Information

What is considered personal information and why would it be collected?  
We collect the following personal information in the course of offering services or providing services to you: Age, Name, Address, and Phone Number, e-mail address, Credit Card details, Evaluations, Comments you provide us, trip destination information, credit card information etc. The collection of this information is done to allow us to provide services to you as requested. We also use this information to: register you to receive newsletters, answer your request for further information about our trips, make a booking, and provide you with information about the Company and/or our services. Furthermore, the personal information allows us to:  
• Understand your needs as a customer and determine eligibility for our products and services.  
• Inform you about our products and services, or those of our partners that we believe may be of interest to you.  
• Provide ongoing service.  
• Comply with the law.  
• Conduct after sales marketing.  
Personal information is not collected unless provided to us. This means you can visit and browse our website without having to provide any personal information.

How is your Personal Information Protected?  
All personal information is stored in secure databases at secure addresses to prevent unauthorized access.

What are our website policies?  
We will acquire personal information such as your name and email address if you subscribe to our electronic newsletter, partake in any surveys or on-line promotions. We do not send unsolicited email.

How does Bookmarkshut use cookies?  
Cookies may be used to help speed up the booking process so you do not need to re-type the same information again and again. We may use cookies to measure website usage such as entry and exit points of visitors, how many people visit a certain section or page and details of searches performed and related information. If you are making a purchase we may also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one page to the next. We do not store any personal information in the cookie, or use it for any other purpose.

How often is this policy updated?  
We will modify this policy in a timely manner when necessary to reflect changes to our Policy. You are obligated to review this Policy from time to time to review these changes
